<DMSEntry>
  <Download>
    <Name>Hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-Bit Edition</Name>
    <PrimaryProduct>Office 2010</PrimaryProduct>
    <DownloadType>Hotfix</DownloadType>
    <MSReleaseType>hotfixes</MSReleaseType>
    <DistributionScope>LimitedDistributionRelease</DistributionScope>
    <PublishingGroup>Office</PublishingGroup>
    <SecurityRelated>No</SecurityRelated>
    <AudienceTypes>
      <AudienceType>IT professionals</AudienceType>
      <AudienceType>business decision makers</AudienceType>
      <AudienceType>developers</AudienceType>
      <AudienceType>home pc users</AudienceType>
      <AudienceType>information workers</AudienceType>
    </AudienceTypes>
    <Categories>
      <Category>Home &amp; Office</Category>
    </Categories>
    <KBArticles>
      <KBArticle>KB2544025</KBArticle>
    </KBArticles>
  </Download>
  <Details Culture="zh-cn">
    <DownloadTitle>Microsoft Office 2010 修补程序 (KB2544025) 64 位版本</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Microsoft Office 2010 修补程序 (KB2544025) 64 位版本</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 64 位版本. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 64 位版本. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>您可以在 Microsoft 知识库文章 &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Microsoft Office 2010 修补程序 (KB2544025) 64 位版本&lt;/a&gt; 中获得有关此更新的特定信息。</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

有关受支持的服务包和 Windows Installer 版本的信息，请参阅 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Microsoft Office 受支持的服务包和 Windows Installer (KB967543)。&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

若要开始下载，请单击 &lt;b&gt;下载&lt;/b&gt; 按钮，然后执行下面其中一项操作，或者从 &lt;b&gt;更改语言&lt;/b&gt; 中选择另一种语言，然后单击 &lt;b&gt;更改&lt;/b&gt;。
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;单击 &lt;b&gt;运行&lt;/b&gt; 立即开始安装。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;单击 &lt;b&gt;保存&lt;/b&gt; 将下载内容保存到您的计算机以便以后安装&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;IT 专业资源&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
在受管理的环境中工作的 IT 专业人员可以在 &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Microsoft Office Desktop Applications TechCenter&lt;/a&gt; 上找到用于部署组织中 Office 更新的完整资源。命令行指令可以在知识库文章 &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Microsoft Self-Extractor 软件包的命令行开关
 (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt; 中找到。</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>修补程序</Keyword>
      <Keyword>性能</Keyword>
      <Keyword>稳定性</Keyword>
      <Keyword>更新</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="sk-sk">
    <DownloadTitle>Rýchla oprava pre produkt Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-bitové vydanie</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Rýchla oprava pre produkt Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-bitové vydanie</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 64-bitové vydanie. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 64-bitové vydanie. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>Konkrétne informácie o tejto aktualizácii sa nachádzajú v článku databázy Microsoft Knowledge Base &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Rýchla oprava pre produkt Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-bitové vydanie&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

Informácie o podporovaných verziách balíkov Service Pack a Inštalátora systému Windows sa nachádzajú v téme 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Podporované balíky Service Pack balíka Microsoft Office a Inštalátora systému Windows (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

Ak chcete spustiť preberanie, kliknite na tlačidlo &lt;b&gt;Prevziať&lt;/b&gt; a potom vykonajte niektorý z nasledujúcich krokov, alebo vyberte z ponuky &lt;b&gt;Zmeniť jazyk&lt;/b&gt; iný jazyk a potom kliknite na tlačidlo &lt;b&gt;Zmeniť&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ak chcete spustiť inštaláciu okamžite, kliknite na tlačidlo &lt;b&gt;Spustiť&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ak chcete uložiť kópiu prevzatého súboru do počítača na inštalovanie neskôr, kliknite na tlačidlo &lt;b&gt;Uložiť&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Zdroje informácií pre profesionálov z oblasti IT&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Profesionáli v oblasti IT pracujúci v spravovaných prostrediach môžu nájsť kompletné zdroje na nasadenie aktualizácií balíka Office v organizácii na lokalite centra &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Microsoft Office Desktop Applications TechCenter&lt;/a&gt;. Pokyny príkazového riadka môžete nájsť v článku databázy Knowledge Base &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Prepínače príkazov v príkazovom riadku pre balíky Microsoft Self-Extractor (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Oprava</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Výkon</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Stabilita</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Aktualizácia</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="sl-si">
    <DownloadTitle>Sprotni popravek za Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-bitna izdaja</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Sprotni popravek za Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-bitna izdaja</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 64-bitna izdaja. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 64-bitna izdaja. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>Določene informacije o teh posodobitvi najdete v članku Microsoftove zbirke znanja na naslovu &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Sprotni popravek za Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-bitna izdaja&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

Če želite več informacij o podprtih servisnih paketih in različicah programa Windows Installer, glejte
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Podprti servisni paketi za Microsoft Office in Windows Installer (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

Če želite začeti prenos, kliknite gumb &lt;b&gt;Prenos&lt;/b&gt; in naredite nekaj od tega ali pa na seznamu &lt;b&gt;Spremeni jezik&lt;/b&gt; izberite drug jezik in nato kliknite &lt;b&gt;Spremeni&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kliknite &lt;b&gt;Zaženi&lt;/b&gt;, če želite namestitev začeti takoj.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kliknite &lt;b&gt;Shrani&lt;/b&gt;, če želite kopirati datoteko za prenos v računalnik in jo namestiti pozneje.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Viri za strokovnjake za IT&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Strokovnjaki za IT, ki delajo v upravljanih okoljih, najdejo vse vire za uvajanje posodobitev za Office v organizaciji na spletnem mestu &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;TechCenter za namizne programe sistema Microsoft Office&lt;/a&gt;. Navodila za ukazno vrstico najdete v članku zbirke znanja z naslovom &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Stikala ukazne vrstice za pakete Microsoft Self-Extractor (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Popravek</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Učinkovitost delovanja</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Stabilnost</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Posodobitev</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="hr-hr">
    <DownloadTitle>Hitni popravak za Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-bitno izdanje</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Hitni popravak za Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-bitno izdanje</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 64-bitno izdanje. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 64-bitno izdanje. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>Konkretne informacije o ovom ažuriranju dostupne su u članku iz Microsoftove baze znanja &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Hitni popravak za Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-bitno izdanje&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

Informacije o podržanim servisnim paketima i verzijama programa Windows Installer potražite u članku 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Servisni paketi koje podržava Microsoft Office i Windows Installer (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

Da biste započeli preuzimanje, kliknite gumb &lt;b&gt;Preuzmi&lt;/b&gt;, a zatim učinite nešto od sljedećeg ili odaberite neki drugi jezik s popisa &lt;b&gt;Promijeni jezik&lt;/b&gt; i kliknite &lt;b&gt;Promijeni&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kliknite &lt;b&gt;Pokreni&lt;/b&gt; da biste odmah započeli instalaciju.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kliknite &lt;b&gt;Spremi&lt;/b&gt; da biste datoteku za preuzimanje kopirali na računalo i instalirali je poslije.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Resursi za IT profesionalce&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
IT profesionalcima koji rade u upravljanim okruženjima na stranici &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Microsoft Office Desktop Applications TechCenter&lt;/a&gt; dostupni su potpuni resursi za implementaciju ažuriranja za Office u tvrtkama i ustanovama. Upute za korištenje naredbenog retka dostupne su u članku iz baze znanja &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Parametri naredbenog retka za Microsoftove pakete s automatskim raspakiravanjem (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Zakrpa</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Performanse</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Stabilnost</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Ažuriranje</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="el-gr">
    <DownloadTitle>Επείγουσα επιδιόρθωση για το Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) Έκδοση 64-Bit</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Επείγουσα επιδιόρθωση για το Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) Έκδοση 64-Bit</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 Έκδοση 64-Bit. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 Έκδοση 64-Bit. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>Μπορείτε να βρείτε συγκεκριμένες πληροφορίες σχετικά με αυτή την ενημέρωση στο άρθρο της Γνωσιακής βάσης της Microsoft &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Επείγουσα επιδιόρθωση για το Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) Έκδοση 64-Bit&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

Για πληροφορίες σχετικά με τα υποστηριζόμενα service pack και τις εκδόσεις του Windows Installer, ανατρέξτε στο άρθρο 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Υποστηριζόμενα Service Pack του Microsoft Office και του Windows Installer (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

Για να ξεκινήσει η λήψη, κάντε κλικ στο κουμπί &lt;b&gt;Λήψη&lt;/b&gt; και, στη συνέχεια, κάντε ένα από τα παρακάτω ή επιλέξτε άλλη γλώσσα από το μενού &lt;b&gt;Αλλαγή γλώσσας&lt;/b&gt; και κάντε κλικ στο κουμπί &lt;b&gt;Αλλαγή&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Κάντε κλικ στο κουμπί &lt;b&gt;Εκτέλεση&lt;/b&gt; για να ξεκινήσει η εγκατάσταση αμέσως.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Κάντε κλικ στο κουμπί &lt;b&gt;Αποθήκευση&lt;/b&gt; για να αντιγράψετε το στοιχείο λήψης στον υπολογιστή σας για να το εγκαταστήσετε αργότερα&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Πόροι επαγγελματιών IT &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Οι επαγγελματίες IT που εργάζονται σε διαχειριζόμενα περιβάλλοντα μπορούν να βρουν ολοκληρωμένους πόρους για ανάπτυξη ενημερώσεων του Office σε έναν οργανισμό στο &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Microsoft Office Desktop Applications TechCenter&lt;/a&gt;. Οδηγίες για τη γραμμή εντολών μπορείτε να τις εντοπίσετε στο άρθρο της Γνωσιακής βάσης &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Διακόπτες της γραμμής εντολών για πακέτα Microsoft Self-Extractor (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Ενημέρωση κώδικα</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Απόδοση</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Σταθερότητα</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Ενημέρωση</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="eu-es">
    <DownloadTitle>Hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-Bit Edition</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-Bit Edition</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 64-Bit Edition. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 64-Bit Edition. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>You can get specific information about this update in the Microsoft Knowledge Base article &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-Bit Edition&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

For information about supported service packs and Windows Installer versions, please see 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Microsoft Office Supported Service Packs and Windows Installer (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

To start the download, click the &lt;b&gt;Download&lt;/b&gt; button and then do one of the following, or select another language from &lt;b&gt;Change Language&lt;/b&gt; and then click &lt;b&gt;Change&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Run&lt;/b&gt; to start the installation immediately.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Save&lt;/b&gt; to copy the download to your computer for installation at a later time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;IT professional resources&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
IT professional working in managed environments can find complete resources for deploying Office updates in an organization on the &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Microsoft Office Desktop Applications TechCenter&lt;/a&gt;. Command line instructions can be found in Knowledge Base article &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Command line switches for Microsoft Self-Extractor packages (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Patch</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Performance</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Stability</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Update</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="pt-pt">
    <DownloadTitle>Correcção para Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) Edição de 64 Bits</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Correcção para Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) Edição de 64 Bits</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 Edição de 64 Bits. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 Edição de 64 Bits. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>É possível obter informações específicas sobre esta actualização no artigo da Base de Dados de Conhecimento Microsoft sobre &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Correcção para Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) Edição de 64 Bits&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

Para obter informações sobre service packs suportados e sobre versões do Windows Installer, consulte o tópico sobre 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Service Packs Suportados do Microsoft Office e Windows Installer (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

Para iniciar a transferência, clique no botão &lt;b&gt;Transferir&lt;/b&gt; e efectue um dos seguintes procedimentos, ou seleccione outro idioma em &lt;b&gt;Alterar Idioma&lt;/b&gt; e clique em &lt;b&gt;Alterar&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clique em &lt;b&gt;Executar&lt;/b&gt; para iniciar a instalação imediatamente.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clique em &lt;b&gt;Guardar&lt;/b&gt; para copiar a transferência para o computador para instalar mais tarde&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Recursos de profissionais de TI&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Os profissionais de TI que trabalham em ambientes geridos podem encontrar recursos completos para a implementação de actualizações do Office numa organização no &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;TechCenter de Aplicações de Ambiente de Trabalho do Microsoft Office&lt;/a&gt;. É possível encontrar instruções de linha de comandos no artigo da Base de Dados de Conhecimento sobre &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Parâmetros da linha de comandos para pacotes do Microsoft Self-Extractor (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Patch</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Desempenho</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Estabilidade</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Actualização</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="it-it">
    <DownloadTitle>Aggiornamento rapido per Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) Versione a 64 bit</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Aggiornamento rapido per Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) Versione a 64 bit</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 Versione a 64 bit. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 Versione a 64 bit. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>Informazioni specifiche su questo aggiornamento sono disponibili nell'articolo della Microsoft Knowledge Base &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Aggiornamento rapido per Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) Versione a 64 bit&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

Per informazioni sui Service Pack supportati e le versioni di Windows Installer, vedere 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Service Pack di Microsoft Office supportati e Windows Installer (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

Per avviare il download, fare clic sul pulsante &lt;b&gt;Scarica&lt;/b&gt;, quindi eseguire una delle operazioni seguenti oppure selezionare un'altra lingua in &lt;b&gt;Cambia lingua&lt;/b&gt; e fare clic su &lt;b&gt;Cambia&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fare clic su &lt;b&gt;Esegui&lt;/b&gt; per avviare subito l'installazione.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Per copiare il download nel computer ed eseguire l'installazione in un secondo momento, fare clic su &lt;b&gt;Salva&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Risorse per i professionisti IT&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
I professionisti IT che lavorano in ambienti gestiti possono trovare risorse complete per la distribuzione degli aggiornamenti di Office all'interno di un'organizzazione nel sito Web &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;TechCenter relativo alle applicazioni desktop Microsoft Office&lt;/a&gt;. Per informazioni relative alla riga di comando, vedere l'articolo della Knowledge Base &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Opzioni della riga di comando per i pacchetti del programma di autoestrazione Microsoft (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Patch</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Prestazioni</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Stabilità</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Aggiornamento</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="ja-jp">
    <DownloadTitle>Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64 ビット版 の修正プログラム</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64 ビット版 の修正プログラム</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 64 ビット版. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 64 ビット版. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>この更新プログラムに関する詳細情報については、マイクロソフト サポート技術情報の記事 &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64 ビット版 の修正プログラム&lt;/a&gt; を参照してください。</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

サポートされるサービス パックおよび Windows インストーラーのバージョンについては、以下の記事を参照してください。
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Microsoft Office Supported Service Packs and Windows Installer (KB967543)&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

ダウンロードを開始するには、[\[]ダウンロード[\]] ボタンをクリックし、以下のいずれかの操作を実行してください。[\[]言語の変更[\]] から [\[]変更[\]] をクリックして、別の言語を選択することもできます。
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[\[]実行[\]] をクリックして、インストールをすぐに実行します。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;[\[]保存[\]] をクリックして、後でインストールできるようにファイルをコンピューターに保存します。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;IT 担当者のためのリソース&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
管理環境で作業する IT 担当者 は、組織への Office 更新プログラムの展開に関する完全なリソースを &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/ja-jp/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Microsoft Office Desktop Applications TechCenter&lt;/a&gt; で参照できます。コマンド ラインの指示については、サポート技術情報の記事 &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Command line switches for Microsoft Self-Extractor packages (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt; を参照してください。</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>パッチ</Keyword>
      <Keyword>パフォーマンス</Keyword>
      <Keyword>安定性</Keyword>
      <Keyword>更新プログラム</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="ca-es">
    <DownloadTitle>Hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-Bit Edition</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-Bit Edition</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 64-Bit Edition. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 64-Bit Edition. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>You can get specific information about this update in the Microsoft Knowledge Base article &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-Bit Edition&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

For information about supported service packs and Windows Installer versions, please see 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Microsoft Office Supported Service Packs and Windows Installer (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

To start the download, click the &lt;b&gt;Download&lt;/b&gt; button and then do one of the following, or select another language from &lt;b&gt;Change Language&lt;/b&gt; and then click &lt;b&gt;Change&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Run&lt;/b&gt; to start the installation immediately.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Save&lt;/b&gt; to copy the download to your computer for installation at a later time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;IT professional resources&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
IT professional working in managed environments can find complete resources for deploying Office updates in an organization on the &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Microsoft Office Desktop Applications TechCenter&lt;/a&gt;. Command line instructions can be found in Knowledge Base article &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Command line switches for Microsoft Self-Extractor packages (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Patch</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Performance</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Stability</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Update</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="da-dk">
    <DownloadTitle>Hotfix til Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-bit version</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Hotfix til Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-bit version</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 64-bit version. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 64-bit version. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>Du kan finde specifikke oplysninger om denne opdatering i Microsoft Knowledge Base-artiklen &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Hotfix til Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-bit version&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

Du kan finde oplysninger om understøttede servicepakker og Windows Installer-versioner under 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Microsoft Office-understøttede servicepakker og Windows Installer (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

Klik på &lt;b&gt;Hent&lt;/b&gt; for at starte overførslen, og gør et af følgende, eller vælg et andet sprog fra &lt;b&gt;Skift sprog&lt;/b&gt;, og klik derefter på &lt;b&gt;Skift&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Klik på &lt;b&gt;Kør&lt;/b&gt; for at starte installationen med det samme.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Klik på &lt;b&gt;Gem&lt;/b&gt; for at kopiere det hentede til computeren, så du kan installere det på et senere tidspunkt.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Ressourcer for it-medarbejdere&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
It-medarbejdere i administrerede miljøer kan finde komplette ressourcer til installation af Office-opdateringer i en organisation på &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Microsoft Office Desktop Applications TechCenter&lt;/a&gt;. Du kan finde kommandolinjeinstruktioner i Knowledge Base-artiklen &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Kommandolinjeparametre til Microsoft Self-Extractor-pakker (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Programrettelse</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Ydeevne</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Stabilitet</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Opdatering</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="gl-es">
    <DownloadTitle>Hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-Bit Edition</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-Bit Edition</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 64-Bit Edition. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 64-Bit Edition. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>You can get specific information about this update in the Microsoft Knowledge Base article &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-Bit Edition&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

For information about supported service packs and Windows Installer versions, please see 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Microsoft Office Supported Service Packs and Windows Installer (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

To start the download, click the &lt;b&gt;Download&lt;/b&gt; button and then do one of the following, or select another language from &lt;b&gt;Change Language&lt;/b&gt; and then click &lt;b&gt;Change&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Run&lt;/b&gt; to start the installation immediately.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Save&lt;/b&gt; to copy the download to your computer for installation at a later time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;IT professional resources&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
IT professional working in managed environments can find complete resources for deploying Office updates in an organization on the &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Microsoft Office Desktop Applications TechCenter&lt;/a&gt;. Command line instructions can be found in Knowledge Base article &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Command line switches for Microsoft Self-Extractor packages (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Patch</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Performance</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Stability</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Update</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="ru-ru">
    <DownloadTitle>Исправление для Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-разрядный выпуск</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Исправление для Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-разрядный выпуск</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 64-разрядный выпуск. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 64-разрядный выпуск. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>Сведения об этом обновлении см. в статье базы знаний Майкрософт &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Исправление для Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-разрядный выпуск&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

Сведения о поддерживаемых пакетах обновления и версиях установщика Windows см. в статье 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Поддерживаемые Microsoft Office пакеты обновления и версии установщика Windows (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

Чтобы начать загрузку, нажмите кнопку &lt;b&gt;Загрузить&lt;/b&gt;, а затем выполните одно из следующих действий или выберите другой язык в списке &lt;b&gt;Выбрать язык&lt;/b&gt; и нажмите кнопку &lt;b&gt;Изменить&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Чтобы сразу начать установку, нажмите кнопку &lt;b&gt;Запустить&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Чтобы скопировать загрузку на свой компьютер для последующей установки, нажмите кнопку &lt;b&gt;Сохранить&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Ресурсы для ИТ-специалистов&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
ИТ-специалисты, работающие в управляемых средах, могут найти полные ресурсы для развертывания обновлений Office в организации на &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Ресурсе для технических специалистов по настольным системам&lt;/a&gt;. Инструкции по использованию командной строки содержатся в статье базы знаний &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Параметры командной строки для пакетов самоизвлечения Майкрософт (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Исправление</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Производительность</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Стабильность</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Обновление</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="de-de">
    <DownloadTitle>Hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-Bit Edition</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-Bit Edition</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 64-Bit Edition. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 64-Bit Edition. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>You can get specific information about this update in the Microsoft Knowledge Base article &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-Bit Edition&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

For information about supported service packs and Windows Installer versions, please see 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Microsoft Office Supported Service Packs and Windows Installer (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

To start the download, click the &lt;b&gt;Download&lt;/b&gt; button and then do one of the following, or select another language from &lt;b&gt;Change Language&lt;/b&gt; and then click &lt;b&gt;Change&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Run&lt;/b&gt; to start the installation immediately.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Save&lt;/b&gt; to copy the download to your computer for installation at a later time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;IT professional resources&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
IT professional working in managed environments can find complete resources for deploying Office updates in an organization on the &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Microsoft Office Desktop Applications TechCenter&lt;/a&gt;. Command line instructions can be found in Knowledge Base article &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Command line switches for Microsoft Self-Extractor packages (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Patch</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Performance</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Stability</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Update</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="zh-tw">
    <DownloadTitle>Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64 位元版本 的 Hotfix</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64 位元版本 的 Hotfix</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 64 位元版本. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 64 位元版本. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>此更新的特定資訊請參閱 Microsoft 知識庫文章 &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64 位元版本 的 Hotfix&lt;/a&gt;。</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

如需受支援的 Service Pack 與 Windows Installer 版本等相關資訊，請參閱 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Microsoft Office 受支援的 Service Pack 與 Windows Installer (KB967543)。&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

若要開始下載，請按一下 [下載] 按鈕，然後執行下列其中一項動作，或從 [變更語言] 選取其他語言，然後按一下 [變更]。
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;按一下 [執行]，立即開始安裝。&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;按一下 [儲存]，將下載複製到電腦，以便稍後執行安裝&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;IT 專業資源&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
在受管理環境中工作的 IT 專業人員，可以在 &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Microsoft Office Desktop Applications TechCenter&lt;/a&gt; 找到完整的資源，以瞭解如何在組織中部署 Office 更新。命令列相關說明，請參閱知識庫文章 &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Microsoft 自我解壓縮程式套件的命令列參數 (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;。</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>修補程式</Keyword>
      <Keyword>效能</Keyword>
      <Keyword>穩定性</Keyword>
      <Keyword>更新</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="th-th">
    <DownloadTitle>โปรแกรมแก้ไขด่วนสำหรับ Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) รุ่น 64 บิต</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>โปรแกรมแก้ไขด่วนสำหรับ Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) รุ่น 64 บิต</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 รุ่น 64 บิต. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 รุ่น 64 บิต. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>คุณสามารถรับข้อมูลเฉพาะเกี่ยวกับโปรแกรมปรับปรุงนี้ได้จากบทความใน Microsoft Knowledge Base &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;โปรแกรมแก้ไขด่วนสำหรับ Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) รุ่น 64 บิต&lt;/a&gt;</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

สำหรับข้อมูลเกี่ยวกับรุ่นของ Service Pack และ Windows Installer ที่สนับสนุน โปรดดูที่
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Microsoft Office Supported Service Packs and Windows Installer (KB967543)&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

เมื่อต้องการเริ่มดาวน์โหลด ให้คลิกปุ่ม &lt;b&gt;ดาวน์โหลด&lt;/b&gt; แล้วทำตามขั้นตอนอย่างใดอย่างหนึ่งต่อไปนี้ หรือเลือกภาษาอื่นจาก &lt;b&gt;เปลี่ยนภาษา&lt;/b&gt; แล้วคลิก &lt;b&gt;เปลี่ยน&lt;/b&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;คลิก &lt;b&gt;เรียกใช้&lt;/b&gt; เพื่อเริ่มการติดตั้งโดยทันที&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;คลิก &lt;b&gt;บันทึก&lt;/b&gt; เพื่อคัดลอกแฟ้มที่ดาวน์โหลดไปยังคอมพิวเตอร์ของคุณเพื่อติดตั้งในภายหลัง&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;ทรัพยากรสำหรับผู้เชี่ยวชาญด้าน IT&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
ผู้เชี่ยวชาญด้าน IT ที่ทำงานอยู่ในระบบที่มีการจัดการสามารถค้นหาทรัพยากรที่สมบูรณ์สำหรับการปรับใช้โปรแกรมปรับปรุง Office ในองค์กรได้ใน &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Microsoft Office Desktop Applications TechCenter&lt;/a&gt; คุณสามารถดูคำแนะนำเกี่ยวกับบรรทัดคำสั่งได้จากบทความใน Knowledge Base &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Command line switches for Microsoft Self-Extractor packages (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>โปรแกรมแก้ไข</Keyword>
      <Keyword>ประสิทธิภาพ</Keyword>
      <Keyword>เสถียรภาพ</Keyword>
      <Keyword>การปรับปรุง</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="kk-kz">
    <DownloadTitle>Hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-Bit Edition</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-Bit Edition</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 64-Bit Edition. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 64-Bit Edition. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>You can get specific information about this update in the Microsoft Knowledge Base article &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-Bit Edition&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

For information about supported service packs and Windows Installer versions, please see 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Microsoft Office Supported Service Packs and Windows Installer (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

To start the download, click the &lt;b&gt;Download&lt;/b&gt; button and then do one of the following, or select another language from &lt;b&gt;Change Language&lt;/b&gt; and then click &lt;b&gt;Change&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Run&lt;/b&gt; to start the installation immediately.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Save&lt;/b&gt; to copy the download to your computer for installation at a later time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;IT professional resources&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
IT professional working in managed environments can find complete resources for deploying Office updates in an organization on the &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Microsoft Office Desktop Applications TechCenter&lt;/a&gt;. Command line instructions can be found in Knowledge Base article &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Command line switches for Microsoft Self-Extractor packages (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Patch</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Performance</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Stability</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Update</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="et-ee">
    <DownloadTitle>Microsoft Office 2010 kiirparandus (KB2544025) 64-bitine väljaanne</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Microsoft Office 2010 kiirparandus (KB2544025) 64-bitine väljaanne</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 64-bitine väljaanne. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 64-bitine väljaanne. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>Selle värskenduse kohta leiate täpsemat teavet Microsofti teabebaasi (Knowledge Base) artiklist &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Microsoft Office 2010 kiirparandus (KB2544025) 64-bitine väljaanne&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

Toetatud hoolduspakettide ja Windows Installeri versioonide kohta leiate teavet artiklist 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Microsoft Office Supported Service Packs and Windows Installer (Microsoft Office'i toetatud hoolduspaketid ja Windows Installer, KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

Allalaadimise käivitamiseks klõpsake nuppu &lt;b&gt;Laadi alla&lt;/b&gt; ja seejärel tehke ühte järgmistest või valige loendist &lt;b&gt;Vaheta keelt&lt;/b&gt; mõni muu keel ja seejärel klõpsake nuppu &lt;b&gt;Muuda&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Installimise koheseks käivitamiseks klõpsake nuppu &lt;b&gt;Käivita&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allalaaditava faili hilisema installimise jaoks arvutisse kopeerimiseks klõpsake nuppu &lt;b&gt;Salvesta&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Ressursid IT-asjatundjatele&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Hallatavates keskkondades töötavad IT-asjatundjad leiavad täielikud ressursid ettevõttes Office'i värskenduste juurutamiseks &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Microsoft Office'i töölauarakenduste tugikeskusest TechCenter&lt;/a&gt;. Käsureajuhised leiate teabebaasi (Knowledge Base) artiklist &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Command line switches for Microsoft Self-Extractor packages (Käsurealülitid Microsofti automaatekstraktoripakettide jaoks, KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Paik</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Jõudlus</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Stabiilsus</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Värskendus</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="pt-br">
    <DownloadTitle>Hotfix do Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) Edição de 64 bits</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Hotfix do Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) Edição de 64 bits</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 Edição de 64 bits. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 Edição de 64 bits. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>Você pode obter informações específicas sobre esta atualização no artigo da Base de Dados de Conhecimento Microsoft &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Hotfix do Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) Edição de 64 bits&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

Para obter informações sobre os service packs e as versões do Windows Installer com suporte, consulte 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Microsoft Office Supported Service Packs and Windows Installer (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

Para iniciar o download, clique no botão &lt;b&gt;Download&lt;/b&gt; e faça o seguinte, ou selecione outro idioma em &lt;b&gt;Alterar Idioma&lt;/b&gt; e clique em &lt;b&gt;Alterar&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clique em &lt;b&gt;Executar&lt;/b&gt; para iniciar a instalação imediatamente.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clique em &lt;b&gt;Salvar&lt;/b&gt; para copiar o download para o seu computador para instalá-lo mais tarde&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Recursos de profissionais de TI&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Um profissional de TI que trabalhe em ambientes gerenciados podem encontrar recursos completos para implantar atualizações do Office em uma organização no &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Microsoft Office Desktop Applications TechCenter&lt;/a&gt;. As instruções de linha de comando podem ser encontradas no artigo da Base de Dados de Conhecimento &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Command line switches for Microsoft Self-Extractor packages (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Patch</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Desempenho</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Estabilidade</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Atualização</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="bg-bg">
    <DownloadTitle>Актуална корекция за Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-битово издание</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Актуална корекция за Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-битово издание</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 64-битово издание. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 64-битово издание. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>Можете да получите конкретна информация за тази актуализация в статията от базата знания на Microsoft &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Актуална корекция за Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-битово издание&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

За повече информация относно поддържаните сервизни пакети и версиите на Windows Installer вж. 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Поддържани сервизни пакети за Microsoft Office и Windows Installer (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

За да започнете изтеглянето, щракнете върху бутона &lt;b&gt;Изтегли&lt;/b&gt; и след това направете едно от следните неща или изберете друг език от &lt;b&gt;Промяна на езика&lt;/b&gt;, след което щракнете върху &lt;b&gt;Промяна&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Щракнете върху &lt;b&gt;Изпълни&lt;/b&gt;, за да стартирате веднага инсталирането.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Щракнете върху &lt;b&gt;Запиши&lt;/b&gt;, за да копирате изтегления файл на вашия компютър за инсталиране по-късно&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Ресурси за ИТ специалисти&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
ИТ специалистите, които работят в управлявани среди, могат да намерят пълните ресурси за разполагане на актуализации на Office в организацията в &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;TechCenter за настолни приложения на Microsoft Office&lt;/a&gt;. Инструкции за команден ред могат да се намерят в статията от базата знания &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Ключове за команден ред за пакетите на програмата за саморазархивиране на Microsoft (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Корекция</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Производителност</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Стабилност</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Актуализация</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="ar-sa">
    <DownloadTitle>إصلاح عاجل لـ Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) إصدار 64 بت</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>إصلاح عاجل لـ Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) إصدار 64 بت</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 إصدار 64 بت. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 إصدار 64 بت. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>يمكنك الحصول على معلومات محددة عن هذا التحديث في مقالة قاعدة معارف Microsoft &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;إصلاح عاجل لـ Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) إصدار 64 بت&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

للحصول على معلومات حول حزم الخدمة المعتمدة وإصدارات Windows Installer، يرجى مراجعة 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;حزم الخدمة المعتمدة من Microsoft Office وWindows Installer (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

لبدء التنزيل، انقر فوق الزر &lt;b&gt;تنزيل&lt;/b&gt; ثم قم بأحد الإجراءات التالية أو حدد لغة أخرى من &lt;b&gt;تغيير اللغة&lt;/b&gt; ثم انقر فوق &lt;b&gt;تغيير&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;انقر فوق &lt;b&gt;تشغيل&lt;/b&gt; لبدء التثبيت على الفور.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;انقر فوق &lt;b&gt;حفظ&lt;/b&gt; لنسخ التنزيل إلى الكمبيوتر لتثبيته في وقت لاحق&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;موارد احترافي تقنية المعلومات&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
يمكن لاحترافي تقنية معلومات يعمل في بيئات مدارة البحث عن موارد كاملة لنشر تحديثات Office في مؤسسة على موقع &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Microsoft Office Desktop Applications TechCenter&lt;/a&gt;. يمكن البحث عن إرشادات سطر الأوامر في المقالة قاعدة المعارف &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Commورموز التبديل لحزم الاستخراج الذاتي من Microsoft (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>تصحيح</Keyword>
      <Keyword>أداء</Keyword>
      <Keyword>استقرار</Keyword>
      <Keyword>تحديث</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="nl-nl">
    <DownloadTitle>Hotfix voor Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-bits versie</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Hotfix voor Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-bits versie</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 64-bits versie. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 64-bits versie. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>U kunt specifieke informatie over deze update verkrijgen in het Microsoft Knowledge Base-artikel &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Hotfix voor Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-bits versie&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

Zie 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Microsoft Office ondersteunde servicepacks en Windows Installer (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt; voor meer informatie over ondersteunde servicepacks en versies van Windows Installer.</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

Als u het downloaden wilt starten, klikt u op de knop &lt;b&gt;Downloaden&lt;/b&gt; en voert u een van de volgende bewerkingen uit, of selecteert u een andere taal in &lt;b&gt;Taal wijzigen&lt;/b&gt; en klikt u vervolgens op &lt;b&gt;Wijzigen&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Klik op &lt;b&gt;Uitvoeren&lt;/b&gt; om de installatie direct te starten.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Klik op &lt;b&gt;Opslaan&lt;/b&gt; als u de download naar uw computer wilt kopiëren om deze op een later tijdstip te installeren&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Bronnen voor IT-professionals&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
IT-professionals die in beheerde omgevingen werken, kunnen volledige bronnen vinden voor het implementeren van Office-updates in een organisatie in het &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Microsoft Office Desktop Applications TechCenter&lt;/a&gt;. Opdrachtregelinstructies kunt u vinden in Knowledge Base-artikel &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Opdrachtregelschakelopties voor Microsoft Self-Extractor-pakketten (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Schakel</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Prestaties</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Stabiliteit</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Update</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="en-us">
    <DownloadTitle>Hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-Bit Edition</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-Bit Edition</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 64-Bit Edition. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 64-Bit Edition. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>You can get specific information about this update in the Microsoft Knowledge Base article &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-Bit Edition&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

For information about supported service packs and Windows Installer versions, please see 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Microsoft Office Supported Service Packs and Windows Installer (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

To start the download, click the &lt;b&gt;Download&lt;/b&gt; button and then do one of the following, or select another language from &lt;b&gt;Change Language&lt;/b&gt; and then click &lt;b&gt;Change&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Run&lt;/b&gt; to start the installation immediately.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Save&lt;/b&gt; to copy the download to your computer for installation at a later time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;IT professional resources&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
IT professional working in managed environments can find complete resources for deploying Office updates in an organization on the &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Microsoft Office Desktop Applications TechCenter&lt;/a&gt;. Command line instructions can be found in Knowledge Base article &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Command line switches for Microsoft Self-Extractor packages (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Patch</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Performance</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Stability</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Update</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="lv-lv">
    <DownloadTitle>Microsoft Office 2010 labojumfails (KB2544025), 64 bitu izdevums</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Microsoft Office 2010 labojumfails (KB2544025), 64 bitu izdevums</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 64 bitu izdevums. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 64 bitu izdevums. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>Detalizētu informāciju par šo atjauninājumu varat iegūt Microsoft zināšanu bāzes rakstā &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Microsoft Office 2010 labojumfails (KB2544025), 64 bitu izdevums&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

Informāciju par atbalstītajām servisa pakotnēm un programmas Windows Installer versijām, lūdzu, skatiet rakstā 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Atbalstītās Microsoft Office servisa pakotnes un programmas Windows Installer versijas (KB967543)&lt;/a&gt; (EN).</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

Lai sāktu lejupielādi, noklikšķiniet uz pogas &lt;b&gt;Lejupielādēt&lt;/b&gt; un pēc tam veiciet kādu no tālāk minētājām darbībām vai sadaļā &lt;b&gt;Mainīt valodu&lt;/b&gt; atlasiet citu valodu un pēc tam noklikšķiniet uz &lt;b&gt;Mainīt&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lai tūlīt sāktu instalēšanu, noklikšķiniet uz &lt;b&gt;Izpildīt&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lai lejupielādes failu nokopētu datorā un instalētu vēlāk, noklikšķiniet uz &lt;b&gt;Saglabāt&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Resursi IT speciālistiem&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
IT speciālists, kas strādā pārvaldāmā programmatūras vidē, visus resursus, kas nepieciešami Office atjauninājumu izvietošanai organizācijā, var iegūt &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Microsoft Office datoru lietojumprogrammu tehniskajā centrā&lt;/a&gt; (EN). Komandrindas instrukcijas ir norādītas zināšanu bāzes rakstā &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Komandrindas slēdži Microsoft pašizvērses pakotnēm (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Ielāps</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Veiktspēja</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Stabilitāte</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Atjauninājums</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="uk-ua">
    <DownloadTitle>Виправлення для Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-розрядний випуск</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Виправлення для Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-розрядний випуск</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 64-розрядний випуск. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 64-розрядний випуск. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>Детальні відомості про це оновлення можна переглянути у статті бази знань Майкрософт &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Виправлення для Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-розрядний випуск&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

Щоб переглянути відомості про підтримувані пакети оновлень і версії інсталятора Windows, див. 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Підтримувані пакети оновлень Microsoft Office та інсталятор Windows (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

Щоб розпочати завантаження, натисніть кнопку &lt;b&gt;Завантажити&lt;/b&gt;, а потім виконайте одну з описаних нижче дій; або виберіть іншу мову зі списку &lt;b&gt;Змінити мову&lt;/b&gt; та натисніть кнопку &lt;b&gt;Змінити&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Натисніть кнопку &lt;b&gt;Виконати&lt;/b&gt; , щоб одразу почати інсталяцію. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Натисніть кнопку &lt;b&gt;Зберегти&lt;/b&gt;, щоб скопіювати заванатаження на комп'ютер та інсталювати пізніше.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Ресурси для IT-фахівців&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
IT-фахівці, які працюють з керованими середовищами, можуть переглянути всі матеріали, що стосуються розгортання оновлень системи Office в організаціях, на сторінці &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Технічний центр застосунків Microsoft Office для настільних комп'ютерів&lt;/a&gt;. У статті бази знань &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Параметри командного рядка для пакетів Microsoft Self-Extractor (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt; (англ. мовою) наведено інструкції для інсталяції за допомогою командного рядка.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Виправлення</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Продуктивність</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Стабільність</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Оновлення</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="es-es">
    <DownloadTitle>Revisión para Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) Edición de 64 bits</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Revisión para Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) Edición de 64 bits</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 Edición de 64 bits. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 Edición de 64 bits. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>Puede obtener información específica sobre esta actualización en el artículo de Microsoft Knowledge Base &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Revisión para Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) Edición de 64 bits&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

Para obtener información acerca de los Service Packs admitidos y las versiones de  Windows Installer, vea 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Microsoft Office Supported Service Packs and Windows Installer (KB967543)&lt;/a&gt; (en inglés).</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

Para iniciar la descarga, haga clic en el botón &lt;b&gt;Descargar&lt;/b&gt; y, a continuación, siga uno de estos procedimientos o seleccione otro idioma  en &lt;b&gt;Cambiar idioma&lt;/b&gt; y haga clic en &lt;b&gt;Cambiar&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Haga clic en &lt;b&gt;Ejecutar&lt;/b&gt; para iniciar la instalación inmediatamente.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Haga clic en &lt;b&gt;Guardar&lt;/b&gt; para copiar la descarga en el equipo y poder instalarla en otro momento&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Recursos para profesionales de TI&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Los profesionales de TI que trabajan en entornos administrados pueden encontrar recursos completos para implementar actualizaciones de Office en una organización en &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Microsoft Office Desktop Applications TechCenter&lt;/a&gt;. Para encontrar instrucciones de la línea de comandos, vea el artículo de Knowledge Base &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Command line switches for Microsoft Self-Extractor packages (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt; (en inglés).</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Revisión</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Rendimiento</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Estabilidad</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Actualización</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="ko-kr">
    <DownloadTitle>Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64비트 버전용 핫픽스</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64비트 버전용 핫픽스</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 64비트 버전. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 64비트 버전. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>이 업데이트에 대한 자세한 내용은 Microsoft 기술 자료 문서 &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64비트 버전용 핫픽스&lt;/a&gt;에서 확인할 수 있습니다.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

지원되는 서비스 팩 및 Windows Installer 버전을 확인하려면
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Microsoft Office Supported Service Packs and Windows Installer&lt;/a&gt;를 참조하십시오.</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

다운로드를 시작하려면 &lt;b&gt;다운로드&lt;/b&gt; 단추를 누른 후 다음 중 하나를 수행하거나 &lt;b&gt;언어 변경&lt;/b&gt;에서 &lt;b&gt;변경&lt;/b&gt;을 클릭하여 다른 언어를 선택하십시오.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt; &lt;b&gt;실행&lt;/b&gt;을 클릭하여 바로 설치를 시작합니다.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;나중에 설치하려면 &lt;b&gt;저장&lt;/b&gt;을 클릭하여 다운로드한 내용을 컴퓨터에 복사합니다.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;IT 전문가 리소스&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
관리되는 환경의 IT 전문가는 &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/ko-kr/office/bb267342"&gt;Microsoft Office 데스크톱 응용 프로그램 TechCenter&lt;/a&gt;에서 조직의 Office 업데이트 배포를 위한 전체 리소스를 확인할 수 있습니다. 명령줄 관련 내용은 기술 자료 문서 &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Command line switches for Microsoft Self-Extractor packages (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;에서 확인하십시오.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>패치</Keyword>
      <Keyword>성능</Keyword>
      <Keyword>안정성</Keyword>
      <Keyword>업데이트</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="sr-SP-Latn">
    <DownloadTitle>Hitna ispravka za Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-bitno izdanje</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Hitna ispravka za Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-bitno izdanje</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 64-bitno izdanje. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 64-bitno izdanje. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>Specifične informacije o ovoj ispravci možete pronaći u članku Microsoft baze znanja &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Hitna ispravka za Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-bitno izdanje&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

Informacije o podržanim servisnim paketima i verzijama programa Windows Installer potražite u članku 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Podržani servisni paketi za Microsoft Office i Windows Installer (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

Da biste započeli preuzimanje, kliknite na dugme &lt;b&gt;Preuzmi&lt;/b&gt; i uradite nešto od sledećeg ili izaberite drugi jezik sa liste &lt;b&gt;Promena jezika&lt;/b&gt; i kliknite na dugme &lt;b&gt;Promeni&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kliknite na dugme &lt;b&gt;Pokreni&lt;/b&gt; da biste odmah započeli instalaciju.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kliknite na dugme &lt;b&gt;Sačuvaj&lt;/b&gt; da biste kopirali preuzimanje na računar radi kasnije instalacije&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Resursi za IT stručnjake&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
IT stručnjaci koji rade u kontrolisanim okruženjima kompletne resurse za primenu Office ispravki u organizaciji mogu pronaći na lokaciji &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Tehnički centar za Microsoft Office aplikacije za računare&lt;/a&gt;. Instrukcije komandne linije možete pronaći u članku baze znanja &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Komutatori komandne linije za Microsoft samoraspakujuće pakete (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Zakrpa</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Performanse</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Stabilnost</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Ispravka</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="cs-cz">
    <DownloadTitle>Oprava hotfix pro Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) (64bitová edice)</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Oprava hotfix pro Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) (64bitová edice)</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 (64bitová edice). This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 (64bitová edice). Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>Konkrétní informace o této aktualizaci získáte v článku znalostní báze Microsoft Knowledge Base &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Oprava hotfix pro Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) (64bitová edice)&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

Informace o podporovaných aktualizacích Service Pack a verzích Instalační služby systému Windows najdete v článku 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Aktualizace Service Pack a Instalační služba systému Windows podporované systémem Microsoft Office (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

Chcete-li spustit stahování, klikněte na tlačítko &lt;b&gt;Stáhnout&lt;/b&gt; a potom postupujte jedním z následujících kroků nebo z rozevíracího seznamu &lt;b&gt;Změnit jazyk&lt;/b&gt; vyberte jiný jazyk a klikněte na tlačítko &lt;b&gt;Změnit&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kliknutím na tlačítko &lt;b&gt;Spustit&lt;/b&gt; spustíte instalaci ihned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kliknutím na tlačítko &lt;b&gt;Uložit&lt;/b&gt; zkopírujete stahovaný soubor do počítače a budete jej moci nainstalovat později.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Zdroje informací pro odborníky v oboru IT&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Odborníci v oboru IT, kteří pracují v řízených prostředích, najdou kompletní zdroje informací k nasazování aktualizací systému Office v organizaci v &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Centru TechCenter pro aplikace systému Microsoft Office pro stolní počítače&lt;/a&gt;. Příkazy příkazového řádku jsou popsány v článku znalostní báze Knowledge Base &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Přepínače příkazového řádku pro samorozbalovací balíčky společnosti Microsoft (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Oprava</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Výkon</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Stabilita</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Aktualizace</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="sv-se">
    <DownloadTitle>Snabbkorrigering för Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-bitarsversion</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Snabbkorrigering för Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-bitarsversion</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 64-bitarsversion. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 64-bitarsversion. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>Du hittar specifik information om den här uppdateringen i Microsoft Knowledge Base-artikeln &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Snabbkorrigering för Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-bitarsversion&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

Information om service pack och Windows Installer-versioner som stöds finns i  
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Service pack och Windows Installer som stöds för Microsoft Office (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

Om du vill påbörja hämtningen klickar du på &lt;b&gt;Hämta&lt;/b&gt; och gör sedan något av följande eller väljer ett annat språk i &lt;b&gt;Ändra språk&lt;/b&gt; och klickar sedan på &lt;b&gt;Ändra&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Klicka på &lt;b&gt;Kör&lt;/b&gt; om du vill påbörja installationen direkt.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Klicka på &lt;b&gt;Spara&lt;/b&gt; om du vill kopiera den hämtade filen till datorn för installation vid ett senare tillfälle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;IT-proffsresurser&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
IT-proffs som arbetar i hanterade miljöer hittar fullständiga resurser för att distribuera Office-uppdateringar i en organisation på &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;TechCenter för Microsoft Office-datorprogram&lt;/a&gt;. Kommandoradsinstruktioner finns i Knowledge Base-artikeln &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Kommandoradsväxlar för självextraherande Microsoft-paket (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Korrigering</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Prestanda</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Stabilitet</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Uppdatering</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="pl-pl">
    <DownloadTitle>Poprawka dla programu Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) wersja 64-bitowa</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Poprawka dla programu Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) wersja 64-bitowa</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 wersja 64-bitowa. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 wersja 64-bitowa. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>Szczegółowe informacje o tej aktualizacji zawiera artykuł z bazy wiedzy Microsoft Knowledge Base &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Poprawka dla programu Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) wersja 64-bitowa&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

Aby uzyskać informacje o obsługiwanych dodatkach Service Pack i wersjach Instalatora Windows, zobacz 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Obsługiwane dodatki Service Pack do pakietu Microsoft Office i wersje Instalatora Windows (KB967543)&lt;/a&gt;.</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

Aby rozpocząć pobieranie, kliknij przycisk &lt;b&gt;Pobierz&lt;/b&gt;, a następnie wykonaj jedną z poniższych czynności lub wybierz inny język w polu &lt;b&gt;Zmień język&lt;/b&gt; i kliknij przycisk &lt;b&gt;Zmień&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kliknij przycisk &lt;b&gt;Uruchom&lt;/b&gt;, aby natychmiast rozpocząć instalację.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kliknij przycisk &lt;b&gt;Zapisz&lt;/b&gt;, aby skopiować pobrany plik na komputer i zainstalować go później.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Zasoby dla informatyków&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Kompletne zasoby przeznaczone dla informatyków pracujących w środowiskach zarządzanych, dotyczące wdrażania aktualizacji pakietu Office w organizacji można znaleźć w &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;witrynie TechCenter aplikacji komputerowych pakietu Microsoft Office&lt;/a&gt;. Instrukcje dotyczące wiersza polecenia zawiera artykuł z bazy wiedzy &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Przełączniki wiersza polecenia dotyczące pakietów programu Microsoft Self-Extractor (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Poprawka</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Wydajność</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Stabilność</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Aktualizacja</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="tr-tr">
    <DownloadTitle>Microsoft Office 2010 Düzeltmesi (KB2544025) 64 Bit Sürüm</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Microsoft Office 2010 Düzeltmesi (KB2544025) 64 Bit Sürüm</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 64 Bit Sürüm. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 64 Bit Sürüm. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>Bu güncelleştirmeyle ilgili bilgileri Microsoft Bilgi Bankası makalesinden bulabilirsiniz &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Microsoft Office 2010 Düzeltmesi (KB2544025) 64 Bit Sürüm&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

Desteklenen hizmet paketleri ve Windows Installer sürümleri hakkında bilgi için bkz. 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Microsoft Office Desteklenen Hizmet Paketleri ve Windows Installer (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

Karşıdan yükleme işlemini başlatmak için &lt;b&gt;Karşıdan Yükle&lt;/b&gt; düğmesini tıklatın ve aşağıdakilerden birini yapın veya &lt;b&gt;Dili Değiştir&lt;/b&gt; seçeneği ile başka bir dil seçip &lt;b&gt;Değiştir&lt;/b&gt;'i tıklatın.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yükleme işlemini hemen başlatmak için &lt;b&gt;Çalıştır&lt;/b&gt;'ı tıklatın.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Karşıdan yüklenecek dosyaları daha sonra yüklenmek üzere bilgisayarınıza kopyalamak için &lt;b&gt;Kaydet&lt;/b&gt;'i tıklatın&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;BT uzmanı kaynakları&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Yönetilen ortamlarda çalışan BT uzmanları, Office güncelleştirmelerini kuruluşa dağıtmaya yönelik tüm kaynakları &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Microsoft Office Desktop Applications TechCenter&lt;/a&gt; adresinden bulabilir. Komut satırı yönergeleri &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Microsoft Self-Extractor paketlerine yönelik komut satırı anahtarları (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt; adlı Bilgi Bankası makalesinden bulunabilir.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Düzeltme eki</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Performans</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Kararlılık</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Güncelleştirme</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="he-il">
    <DownloadTitle>תיקון חם עבור Microsoft Office 2010‏ (KB2544025)‏ מהדורת 64 סיביות</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>תיקון חם עבור Microsoft Office 2010‏ (KB2544025)‏ מהדורת 64 סיביות</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 מהדורת 64 סיביות. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 מהדורת 64 סיביות. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>באפשרותך לקבל מידע ספציפי אודות עדכון זה במאמר Microsoft Knowledge Base‏ &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;תיקון חם עבור Microsoft Office 2010‏ (KB2544025)‏ מהדורת 64 סיביות&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

לקבלת מידע אודות מהדורות Service Pack נתמכות וגירסאות Windows Installer, ראה 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;מהדורות Service Pack נתמכות של Microsoft Office ו- Windows Installer‏ (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

כדי להתחיל את ההורדה, לחץ על לחצן &lt;b&gt;הורד&lt;/b&gt; ולאחר מכן בצע אחת מהפעולות הבאות, או בחר שפה אחרת מתוך &lt;b&gt;שנה שפה&lt;/b&gt; ולאחר מכן לחץ על &lt;b&gt;שנה&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;לחץ על &lt;b&gt;הפעל&lt;/b&gt; כדי להתחיל בהתקנה מייד.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;לחץ על &lt;b&gt;שמור&lt;/b&gt; כדי להעתיק את ההורדה למחשב שלך לצורך התקנה במועד מאוחר יותר.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;משאבים לאנשי IT&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
אנשי IT שעובדים בסביבות מנוהלות יכולים למצוא משאבים מלאים לפריסת עדכוני Office בארגון ב- &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Microsoft Office Desktop Applications TechCenter&lt;/a&gt;. ניתן למצוא הוראות שורת פקודה במאמר Knowledge Base‏ &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;בוררי שורת פקודה לחבילות חילוץ עצמי של Microsoft‏ (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>תיקון</Keyword>
      <Keyword>ביצועים</Keyword>
      <Keyword>יציבות</Keyword>
      <Keyword>עדכון</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="nb-no">
    <DownloadTitle>Hurtigreparasjon for Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-biters utgave</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Hurtigreparasjon for Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-biters utgave</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 64-biters utgave. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 64-biters utgave. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>Du kan få spesifikk informasjon om denne oppdateringen i Microsoft Knowledge Base-artikkelen &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Hurtigreparasjon for Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-biters utgave&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

For informasjon om støttede oppdateringspakker og Windows Installer-versjoner, se 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Støttede oppdateringspakker for Microsoft Office og Windows Installer (KB967543). (Denne artikkelen kan være på engelsk.)&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

Du starter nedlastingen ved å klikke &lt;b&gt;Last ned&lt;/b&gt; og deretter gjøre ett av følgende. Du kan også velge et annet språk under &lt;b&gt;Endre språk&lt;/b&gt; og deretter klikke &lt;b&gt;Endre&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Klikk &lt;b&gt;Kjør&lt;/b&gt; for å starte installeringen umiddelbart.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Klikk &lt;b&gt;Lagre&lt;/b&gt; for å kopiere nedlastingen til datamaskinen for installering senere&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Ressurser for IT-teknikere&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
IT-teknikere som arbeider i styrte miljøer, kan finne komplette ressurser for å distribuere Office-oppdateringer i en organisasjon på &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;TechCenter for Microsoft Office-skrivebordsprogrammer&lt;/a&gt;. Du kan finne kommandolinjeinstruksjoner i Knowledge Base-artikkelen &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Kommandolinjebrytere for selvutpakkende pakker fra Microsoft (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;. (Denne artikkelen kan være på engelsk.)</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Korrigering</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Ytelse</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Stabilitet</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Oppdatering</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="ro-ro">
    <DownloadTitle>Remediere rapidă pentru Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) Ediţie pe 64 de biţi</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Remediere rapidă pentru Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) Ediţie pe 64 de biţi</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 Ediţie pe 64 de biţi. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 Ediţie pe 64 de biţi. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>Pentru informaţii specifice despre această actualizare, consultaţi articolul din Baza de cunoştinţe Microsoft &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Remediere rapidă pentru Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) Ediţie pe 64 de biţi&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

Pentru informaţii despre pachetele service pack şi versiunile de Windows Installer acceptate, consultaţi 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Pachete service pack Microsoft Office acceptate şi Windows Installer (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

Pentru a începe descărcarea, faceţi clic pe butonul &lt;b&gt;Descărcare&lt;/b&gt; şi apoi alegeţi una dintre variantele care urmează sau selectaţi altă limbă din &lt;b&gt;Modificare limbă&lt;/b&gt; şi apoi faceţi clic pe &lt;b&gt;Modificare&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Faceţi clic pe &lt;b&gt;Executare&lt;/b&gt; pentru a începe imediat instalarea.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Faceţi clic pe &lt;b&gt;Salvare&lt;/b&gt; pentru a copia descărcarea pe computerul dvs. şi a o instala ulterior&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Resurse pentru profesionişti IT&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Profesioniştii IT care lucrează în medii gestionate pot găsi resurse complete pentru implementarea actualizărilor Office în cadrul unei organizaţii în &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/ro-ro/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;TechCenter pentru aplicaţii desktop Microsoft Office&lt;/a&gt;. Instrucţiunile pentru executarea în linie de comandă se găsesc în articolul &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203/ro"&gt;Parametri în linia de comandă pentru pachetele Microsoft Self-Extractor (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt; din Baza de cunoştinţe.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Corecţie</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Performanţă</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Stabilitate</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Actualizare</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="sr-SP-Cyrl">
    <DownloadTitle>Hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-Bit Edition</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-Bit Edition</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 64-Bit Edition. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 64-Bit Edition. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>You can get specific information about this update in the Microsoft Knowledge Base article &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-Bit Edition&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

For information about supported service packs and Windows Installer versions, please see 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Microsoft Office Supported Service Packs and Windows Installer (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

To start the download, click the &lt;b&gt;Download&lt;/b&gt; button and then do one of the following, or select another language from &lt;b&gt;Change Language&lt;/b&gt; and then click &lt;b&gt;Change&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Run&lt;/b&gt; to start the installation immediately.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Save&lt;/b&gt; to copy the download to your computer for installation at a later time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;IT professional resources&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
IT professional working in managed environments can find complete resources for deploying Office updates in an organization on the &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Microsoft Office Desktop Applications TechCenter&lt;/a&gt;. Command line instructions can be found in Knowledge Base article &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Command line switches for Microsoft Self-Extractor packages (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Patch</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Performance</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Stability</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Update</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="fr-fr">
    <DownloadTitle>Correctif pour Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) Édition 64 bits</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Correctif pour Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) Édition 64 bits</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 Édition 64 bits. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 Édition 64 bits. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>Vous pouvez obtenir des informations spécifiques sur cette mise à jour dans l’article de la base de connaissances &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Correctif pour Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) Édition 64 bits&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

Pour plus d’informations sur les packs de service pris en charge et les versions de Windows Installer, consultez l’article 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Windows Installer et Service packs Microsoft Office pris en charge (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

Pour commencer le téléchargement, cliquez sur le bouton &lt;b&gt;Télécharger&lt;/b&gt;, puis effectuez l’une des opérations suivantes ou sélectionnez une autre langue à l’aide de l’option &lt;b&gt;Modifier la langue&lt;/b&gt;, puis cliquez sur &lt;b&gt;Modifier&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cliquez sur &lt;b&gt;Exécuter&lt;/b&gt; pour commencer l’installation immédiatement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cliquez sur &lt;b&gt;Enregistrer&lt;/b&gt; pour copier le téléchargement vers votre ordinateur et effectuer l’installation ultérieurement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Ressources pour les professionnels de l’informatique&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Les professionnels de l’informatique qui travaillent dans des environnements gérés peuvent trouver l’ensemble des ressources sur le déploiement des mises à jour Office dans une organisation sur le site &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/fr-fr/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Applications de bureau Microsoft Office - TechCenter&lt;/a&gt;. Des instructions de ligne de commande sont disponibles dans l’article de la base de connaissances &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Commutateurs de ligne de commande pour les packages Microsoft Self-Extractor (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Correctif</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Performance</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Stabilité</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Mise à jour</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="fi-fi">
    <DownloadTitle>Hotfix-korjaus: Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-bittinen versio</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Hotfix-korjaus: Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-bittinen versio</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 64-bittinen versio. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 64-bittinen versio. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>Tämän päivityksen yksityiskohtaiset tiedot löytyvät Microsoft Knowledge Base -artikkelista &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Hotfix-korjaus: Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64-bittinen versio&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

Tuetuista service packeista ja Windows Installer -versioista on tietoja tässä artikkelissa: 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Microsoft Officen tuetut service packit ja Windows Installer (KB967543).&lt;/a&gt;</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

Voit aloittaa latauksen napsauttamalla &lt;b&gt;Lataa&lt;/b&gt;-painiketta ja valitsemalla sitten jommankumman alla mainituista vaihtoehdoista tai valitsemalla &lt;b&gt;Vaihda kieli&lt;/b&gt; -kohdassa toisen kielen ja valitsemalla sitten &lt;b&gt;Vaihda&lt;/b&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Valitse &lt;b&gt;Suorita&lt;/b&gt;, jos haluat tehdä asennuksen heti.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Valitse &lt;b&gt;Tallenna&lt;/b&gt;, jos haluat kopioida latauspaketin omaan tietokoneeseesi myöhemmin tapahtuvaa asennusta varten&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;IT-ammattilaisen resurssit&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Hallituissa ympäristöissä työskentelevät IT-ammattilaiset voivat hakea kaikki organisaation Office-pävitysten käyttöönotossa tarvittavat resurssit seuraavasta paikasta: &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Microsoft Office Desktop Applications TechCenter&lt;/a&gt;. Komentoriviohjeet on annettu Knowledge Base -artikkelissa &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;Microsoftin automaattisesti purkautuvien pakettien komentorivivalitsimet (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Korjaustiedosto</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Suorituskyky</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Vakaus</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Päivitä</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Details Culture="hu-hu">
    <DownloadTitle>Gyorsjavítás: Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64 bites kiadás</DownloadTitle>
    <ShortName>Gyorsjavítás: Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64 bites kiadás</ShortName>
    <ShortDescription>Microsoft has released a hotfix for Microsoft Office 2010 64 bites kiadás. This hotfix provides the latest fixes to Microsoft Office 2010 64 bites kiadás. Additionally, this hotfix contains stability and performance improvements.</ShortDescription>
    <LongDescription>Erről a frissítésről részletes információt olvashat a Microsoft Tudásbázis következő cikkében: &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/2544025"&gt;Gyorsjavítás: Microsoft Office 2010 (KB2544025) 64 bites kiadás&lt;/a&gt;.</LongDescription>
    <SystemRequirements>&lt;br/&gt;

Ha többet szeretne tudni a támogatott szervizcsomagokról és Windows Installer-verziókról, olvassa el a 
&lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/967543"&gt;Microsoft Office által támogatott szervizcsomagok és Windows Installer-verziók (KB967543)&lt;/a&gt; című cikket.</SystemRequirements>
    <Instructions>&lt;br /&gt;

A letöltés megkezdéséhez kattintson a &lt;b&gt;Letöltés&lt;/b&gt; gombra, és végezze el az alábbi műveletek egyikét, vagy válasszon másik nyelvet a &lt;b&gt;Nyelv megváltoztatása&lt;/b&gt; listából, és kattintson a &lt;b&gt;Változtat&lt;/b&gt; gombra.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A telepítés azonnali megkezdéséhez kattintson a &lt;b&gt;Futtatás&lt;/b&gt; gombra.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ha a fájlt később szeretné telepíteni, a &lt;b&gt;Mentés&lt;/b&gt; gombra kattintva mentse a számítógépre.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Források informatikusoknak&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
A felügyelt környezetekben dolgozó informatikai szakemberek mindenre kiterjedő forrásokat találhatnak az Office-frissítések szervezetbeli üzembe helyezéséhez a &lt;a href="http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/office/desktop/default.aspx"&gt;Microsoft Office Desktop Applications TechCenter&lt;/a&gt; webhelyen. A parancssori kapcsolók leírását megtalálhatják a Tudásbázis következő cikkében: &lt;a href="http://support.microsoft.com/kb/912203"&gt;A Microsoft Self-Extractor önkibontó használatával létrehozott szoftvertelepítési programcsomag, frissítőcsomag vagy gyorsjavítás által támogatott parancssori kapcsolók ismertetése (KB912203)&lt;/a&gt;.</Instructions>
    <Keywords>
      <Keyword>Office</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2010</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Javítás</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Teljesítmény</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Stabilitás</Keyword>
      <Keyword>Frissítés</Keyword>
      <Keyword>2544025</Keyword>
    </Keywords>
  </Details>
  <Releases>
    <OperatingSystems>
      <OperatingSystem>Windows Server 2003</OperatingSystem>
      <OperatingSystem>Windows Vista</OperatingSystem>
      <OperatingSystem>Windows XP</OperatingSystem>
      <OperatingSystem>Windows 7</OperatingSystem>
    </OperatingSystems>
    <Files>
      <File Culture="All">office2010-kb2544025-fullfile-x64-glb.exe</File>
    </Files>
  </Releases>
</DMSEntry>